23.976 English RETAiL from SDH sync © 24.06.2021
- Witch ! Witch ! - Witch !
Please forgive me .
Witch ! Witch !
Witch !
Forgive me .
Witch ! Witch !
- Witch ! Witch ! - Witch ! Witch !
I need to be here .
- Witch ! Witch ! - I need to be here .
It 's my fault . I know .
Witch ! Witch !
Forgive me .
- Oh , shit ! Thanks . I didn 't even see that . - Neither did I.
People say seeing is believing ,
but for me , that 's not entirely true .
I lost my sight when I was five years old .
Those memories of what I have seen have faded so much
that I doubt I 'd even recognise myself any more .
Now I see using my other senses .
I can smell the rain before it drops , but I can 't watch it fall .
I can feel the sun on my face , but I can 't see it rise or set .
I want to see the world like everyone else .
To see the sun , the rain and music .
Oh , I bet music looks beautiful .
Thank you , thank you . Thank you .
Let 's try . Tastes good .
- Happy birthday . - Thank you .
- Good evening , Miss Wells . - Hi , Miguel . Thank you .
You 're welcome .
- Lilies . - New , just this morning .
Myself , I prefer roses , but ... You 're the first one that 's noticed .
Nervous about tomorrow ?
No .
Actually , I 've never been so scared in my entire life .
Listen , the night before my mother 's surgery , she drank two glasses of sherry .
Steady as a rock the next day .
Thank you .
- Good night . - Good night .
Based on the Chinese-Language Motion Picture " The Eye "
( aka " Gin Gwai " aka " Jian Gui " ) By Jo Jo Yuet-Chun Hui , Oxide Pang and Danny Pang
This is Dr Haskins ' office calling from County General .
Your procedure is still on schedule for tomorrow .
Be sure to arrive at the hospital four hours early for pre-op .
Thank you .
Hi , sweetie , it 's your sister .
My flight gets in at 5am . The whole crew 's got a layover ,
so I 'll find someone to give me a ride straight to the hospital .
I love you , Sydney , can 't wait to see you . Bye .
12 : 10am .
The Eye ( 2008 )
I 'd like to see about moving her ...
.. pressure on the eyes ...
All right . How 's Mrs Hillman doing ?
- Hello ? - Shh !
Martha will hear you . She 's on from 12 to six ,
and , well , she takes away my MMs if I get out of bed .
I 'm Alicia . I 'm holding out my hand to shake .
Oh . I 'm Sydney .
I know . Sydney Wells . I , er , kind of read your chart .
You had a cornea transplant .
- How old are you ? - Nine and a half .
There 's this , like , well , golf-ball thing , inside my head .
And it made me so dizzy I couldn 't even ride my bike .
So the doctors are trying to get it out . When do you get to see ?
Pretty soon , I think .
Good , I 'll come back , then you can take a look at me .
OK .
- Bye , nice to meet you . - Bye .
Dr Stewart , ICU four , please . Dr Stewart ICU four , please .
- I 'm starting to lose the feeling in my fingers . - Me , too .
OK . If you 'll excuse me , please ?
All right .
All right , Sydney , I 'm gonna take the bandages off .
- OK . - You ready ?
- Yeah . - OK .
That 's one .
That 's two .
OK .
Now , I 'm gonna help you open your eyes , very slowly .
- Ready ? - OK .
Slowly , slowly , slowly .
Come on .
Good . Now , tell me what you see .
I can 't ...
I 'm gonna hold up my hand ,
and I want you to tell me how many fingers I have up , OK ?
Wow , those are fingers .
Yes , they are .
All right , here we go .
Five .
- All of them ? - Yes , very good .
- Sydney ? - Yeah ?
I want you to try and reach out and grab my hand .
OK ?
It 's OK , it 's OK .
Not everybody can do this right away . It 's OK .
- It burns a little . - Is that normal ?
Yeah , it 's perfectly normal .
Very good .
- Thank you . - Yeah .
Am I how you pictured ?
I don 't know . You 're really blurry .
- I wish Mom and Dad were here to see this . - Yeah .
I think I wanted this more than you , Sydney .
Helen , you were 12 .
I waited for this for 15 years ,
I thought I 'd ... I 'd feel a sense of ...
Sort of like ...
It 's not your fault .
Hey ...
I 'm sorry .
You just need time . You 'll see .
- Good night . - Good night .
- I love you . - I love you , too .
Sydney , can you see me ?
Don 't feel bad if you can 't .
What 's that on your head ?
It 's a bandanna . My grandpa gave it to me .
You know , maybe tomorrow we can take a walk
and I can show you the park outside .
- Palm trees ... - Alicia .
Oh , coming ...
Sasquatch . Got to go .
Bye .
Please , I don 't want to go .
Mrs Hillman ?
Where are you taking her ?
Freezing .
I 'm freezing .
I 'm freezing . Freezing .
Freezing . I 'm freezing !
Where 's Mrs Hillman ?
Oh , I 'm sorry . She passed away last night .
Mm . Everything is just perfect .
You 're recovering quite nicely .
And the tearing has stopped ?
- Think so , yeah . - OK . Good .
Erm ... So whose eyes were these ?
- Excuse me ? - My , er ... My donor .
I 'm afraid I can 't help you with that , Sydney .
These are your eyes now and they 're working .
- Shouldn 't matter where they came from . - Ah .
- That hurt ? - Yeah , a little .
When will I be able to see more clearly ?
Well , it varies with each patient .
Couple of days , couple of weeks .
But your vision itself isn 't the issue .
Since you 've been blind so long , I 'm going to refer you to a specialist .
Paul Faulkner . He 'll help you .
- It 's OK , I got it . - Oh !
- You all right ? - Yeah .
All right . Have a nice day off tomorrow .
- Thanks , Sydney . - OK .
- Hi . - Hey .
Are you ready to be my tour guide ?
You 're leaving ?
Yeah , I 'm afraid they 've had enough of me here .
This is my sister , Helen . Helen , this is Alicia .
- Hi . - Hi .
Hey , can we get a pictuire together ?
- Of course . - Here , I 'll do it .
OK .
I know you 're scared , Sydney . Don 't be .
The world , it 's ... it 's really beautiful .
OK , smile .
My carry-on 's in the trunk . I could just sleep on your couch , you know .
I could make you meals and clean . We could go to some art galleries .
Is it too much for you ? I mean , shall we pull over or something ?
- Just say the word , OK ? - No , no , no . We can talk every day .
You can come over and check on me , I just ...
I really think I just need to do this on my own , OK ?
OK , I understand .
I got some new lamps for your place .
- Oh , thanks . - I put them in .
- Here , I 'll do it . - OK .
Surprise !
This is too soon , I know .
- I don 't know what I was thinking . - No , no , no . It 's OK , it 's OK .
Do I know any of you ?
Welcome home .
- Oh , hi , Jim . How are you ? - How you doing ?
- Great to see you . - Nice to see you , too .
Sydney , it 's Brett ! Welcome home .
- Oh , thank you . - Wonderful .
- Hey , Syd , it 's me , Alex , from upstairs . - Oh , Alex . Wow , nice to see you .
It 's your cousin , Sarah .
Oh , Sarah ! It 's been so long .
- I 'm so happy . - Recognise my voice ?
- Hi , Cynthia . - How 'd you know it was me ?
How could I not , Cynthia ?
What 's up , girl ?
Oh , Richard , hi .
Hey , how you doing ?
- So , this is what bald looks like . - Mm-hm .
Hey , Sydney , how are you ?
Miguel ? How are you ?
- You look good . - Oh , honey , I 'm so happy for you .
- Honey , how are you ? It 's Amanda . - Sydney , it 's Kisha . How are you feeling ?
- Oh , you look great . - Hey .
Honey , are you OK ? Do you need some water or anything ?
Yeah , I 'm gonna go to the kitchen .
- Why don 't you stay with the guests ? - Socialise .
Oh , thank you , guys , for coming .
1 : 06am .
- Hi . - Hi .
Sorry I 'm late .
That 's Henry .
- I 'm Paul . - Sydney .
Have a seat .
You damaged your corneas when you were five ?
Yeah , my sister and I were playing with firecrackers .
I tried a transplant when I was 12 , but I rejected them .
Hm . Stem cell research . Changed the game .
- Is that why you tried again ? - Well , no .
My sister was really the one who kept up with all that stuff .
These are Dr Haskins ' test results .
There 's nothing physically wrong with you , the operation went flawlessly ,
- .. but you 're probably in for a shock . - Why ?
You already filter information from sound , smell and touch .
But now , you 're gonna be assaulted
by a million things you never even knew existed .
It 's a whole new level of confusion .
Do I look here , here ?
Is that bright thing important ,
or this dark one , moving toward me , away from me , dangerous or not ?
As long as your eyes are open , it 's just too many distractions .
I mean , how do you concentrate ?
I 'm talking to you and you 're looking at that woman ,
and you 're thinking , " Is she gonna eat that ? "
That 's a pineapple , by the way , you cut it open .
I like pineapple .
Sorry .
Anyway because you can see ,
people are gonna expect you to be able to do things that you can 't do .
Read signs recognise body language ,
people 's gestures , facial expressions ,
or just get out of their way .
Your eyes will want to dominate how you perceive the world ,
but you can 't fully trust them , not yet .
In the next few weeks I 'm gonna help you to see the world like it really is , OK ?
Some of it 's gonna be wonderful , a lot of it 's gonna be difficult .
But the main thing is to be prepared , and that 's where I come in .
We 're in this together .
You should have more than enough time . Yeah ...
You scared me .
- Hey . - Have you seen my report card ?
Your report card ?
Do you live here , sweetie ?
My father will be so mad at me .
H.. Have you seen my report card ?
Oh .
Sorry .
Let 's take five .
I 'm sorry , I don 't ... I don 't know what 's wrong with me .
Relax . You 're pushing too hard .
You know , when I first went to London to work with the Philharmonic , I was so nervous .
In Prague , I was a big fish .
In London , one of the hundreds .
But you did so well in London .
I never thought I would be ready .
But when it was time to go on , everything faded away .
It was just me .
I told you I was going to do it if you didn 't come back .
I wasted so much time being worried , when there was nothing to worry about .
- Who am I ... - And now our spring concert series ...
I 'm gonna do it .
Sydney , will you be ready ? We 're all counting on you .
I 'll be ready .
- I 'm sure you 'll be . - Yeah .
Number 42 .
42 ? That 's us .
- You sit , I 'll take it . - Thank you .
- 42 ? - Yeah .
- Is it salmon ? - No , it 's ham .
Oh , I wanted the salmon ... I 'm sorry .
- Oh . - Can you change it ?
You think I 'm just gonna let you go ?
You think I 'm not gonna do something ?
That 's it , right ?
- I 'm gonna do it . - I 'm sorry ?
I told you I was gonna do it .
Don 't go .
Are you all right , miss ?
- Yeah . - That 's great .
- Look , it 's really sweet , you know ? - Double cappuccino .
What happened ?
There ... there was a woman , she came at me .
What woman ? What woman ?
Christ , Sydney , get a hold of yourself , please .
Sorry . I 'm sorry .
- I apologise . - It 's all right .
Witch ! Witch !
- Witch ! Witch ! - Witch !
- Preliminary results from the refractive analysis . - And that 's good , right ?
Well ...
From the latest results ,
there 's nothing wrong with your eyes .
Well , maybe there 's something wrong with the tests .
Tests only gauged the fact that you gave no abnormal responses .
Creative ones , yeah . The kind that artists and musicians give ,
but , last I checked , you are a musician .
I 'm sure other musicians don 't see what I 've been seeing .
Come with me .
I 'm not an idiot . I understand what you 're telling me .
My brain is having to relearn how to decode the world around me .
But that 's very different from me seeing things that don 't seem to be real .
- How ? - Look .
You 're real , OK ?
You 're here .
My perspective and focus is off , but you 're real .
I can see you .
We see what we look at .
But the way that we see things is affected by what we know .
And there 's a lot around you that you can 't make sense of yet .
What are you saying to me ?
You think I 'm making this up ?
You think I want this to be happening to me ?
You think you 're not gonna be able to push through this .
You think you were better off before , more special .
Well , you just discovered that now you 're like the rest of us .
Stop .
You know , when we first met ,
I didn 't think you were such an ass .
That 's cos you didn 't know how to spot one .
See ? Progress .
Have a good evening , Ms Cheung .
Ah ! Miss Wells .
Your new TV is here .
My buddy from the cable company hooked you up .
Thank you , Miguel .
And welcome to the 200-channel universe .
- Thanks . Bye . - Good night .
Ohh ...
God !
I guess I should have known .
You knew my history when we got engaged .
I know . But I thought that was just a kind of experiment ...
This weekend only , Jameson 's special prices ...
The dining ...
Careful .
Check out your new town ?
Seemms spread out . It 's kind of a hike .
You 'll get your licence back in six months .
It 's not so long .
Open the door !
Let me out ! Don 't go !
Don 't go !
No ! No !
Stay there !
I won 't go out .
Except for you .
Hi this is Helen . I 'm out of town till Saturday .
So if you need to contact me , do so after the beep .
Hey , it 's Syd . Er ... Please call me .
Whoa ! What are you doing ?
Oh , my God .
.. stepped off the sidewalk ...
She 's not breathing .
Hi , you 've reached the cellphone of Dr Paul Faulkner .
Leave a message after the beep .
Hi , Paul , erm , it 's Sydney .
I 'm at a Chinese restaurant on the corner of Fourth and Figueroa .
Something 's happening to me .
And I need you to come .
Please .
Excuse me ?
Sydney ! Sydney ! It 's me . It 's me .
- It 's me . - Oh ...
This place ...
- No ... - Shh .
No , no , no . It was just here . It was just here .
- What are you talking about ? - This place , I was ... I was ...
There was a fire in here . There was a fire in here weeks ago .
Five people were killed . It was in the newspapers , it was all over the press .
- I was here , I was just here . - Hey .
Oh , where is this place ?
- What 's wrong ? - Everything 's wrong . Everything 's wrong .
My apartment keeps changing .
It was filled with smoke ,
- .. and then I was attacked by this man ... - What do you mean ?
He was on fire , and then he was gone .
Everything was gone , and so I had to get out of there .
And I was walking down the street , and then this ...
This woman walks through me .
She walked right through me .
And I saw the shadow .
I saw it before , at the hospital .
It 's some kind of ... of escort
that takes people away when they 're dead .
There 's something so angry about them .
They ... they ...
They don 't want to be seen .
And then this ...
I see people , like nothing is wrong .
Only they don 't seem to see me .
- Sydney , listen to me . - I 'm seeing things that aren 't real .
I 'm seeing things I shouldn 't see .
I 'm dreaming things I 've never seen .
This surgery was supposed to make me normal .
Sydney , your eyes are not the problem .
These eyes are not my eyes .
- Yes , they are . - No , they 're not .
Yes , they are .
- No , they 're not . - Yes , they are . Listen to me .
You 've got a disorder , all right ?
We 've got to teach your brain
how to separate out these ghost images from the real thing .
You 're not listening to me .
I 'm not seeing ghost images .
- I see ... - What ? Dead people ?
Rooms that change , phantom escorts ,
whatever it is that you believe you 're seeing , it 's not real !
It 's ... it 's not .
It 's not real .
You don 't believe me .
I wanna help you .
How can you ?
How can you if you don 't believe me ?
- Yeah . What ? - What 's ...
You getting on , or what ?
You 're crazy .
Oh , it 's not real ! No , no . It 's not real !
It 's not real . It 's not real . It 's not real .
It 's not real ! It 's not real ! It 's not real !
It 's not real ! It 's not real ! It 's not real ! It 's not real !
It 's not real ! It 's not real !
Have you seen my report card ?
- Have you seen my report card ? - No ! I already told you .
- Have you seen my report card ? - Stop asking me .
No .
No ! No !
Have you seen my report card ?
He 's so mad at me .
Have you seen my ...
Have you seen my report card ?
Ow ! Ow !
1 : 06am .
It 's Helen . I 'm on my way to the airport . Are you OK ?
Will you call me ? On my cell , OK ? Please .
You 're scaring me , sweetie . Pick up .
OK , I 'm gonna call someone .
I 'm gonna call someone unless you pick up , Sydney .
Sydney ?
Miss Wells .
It 's Paul . Are you in there ?
The doorman 's gonna let me in , all right ?
Miss Wells ?
- Can you give us a minute ? - Sure .
Your sister called . She said you hadn 't answered the phone in days .
What is this ? You wanna be blind again ?
At least do it right . When you were blind , you had a life .
You were engaged in the world , you had a job .
But what is this ? You get scared and you just drop out ,
and run back to your room , turn off the lights ?
So what now ?
I 'm taking you to the hospital to get this cut sewn up .
Is it really necessary ?
Yeah .
We 're gonna figure this out .
Dr Miner to Emergency . Dr Miner to Emergency .
Dr Harvey to ...
I think you should keep her here overnight . Here 's my telephone number .
Sydney Wells ,
you 're back .
Alicia ?
What are you doing here ?
My golf ball 's gone , Sydney Wells .
- What ? - I have to go now .
Wait , hang on .
Alicia .
Alicia ?
I know you 're scared .
Don 't be , because the world really is beautiful .
No .
No ! Alicia .
Don 't go with him !
Alicia !
How are you ?
Whatever 's happening , there 's nothing that can 't be fixed .
Morning .
- Morning . - How 's the hand ?
It 's fine .
Alicia 's mother wanted you to have this .
Said she talked about you all the time . Said she was smiling up to the very end .
Oh .
Who is she ?
That 's you , Sydney .
That 's not me .
Of course it is . Who else would it be ?
Sydney , what are you doing ?
Sydney .
You 're scaring me .
What do you see ?
Cellular memory , based on the theory
that all living tissues have the capacity to remember .
Cellular memory explains how energy and information from a donor 's tissue
can be transferred consciously or unconsciously to the recipient .
Recently , recipients of organ transplants
have begun to report episodes of newfound memories ,
thoughts , emotions and characteristics
that are often associated to the original donor .
- Paul . - I can 't talk now , I got to go to a meeting .
Listen , there is no history of schizophrenia in my family .
I 've never suffered from any mental condition .
Not depression , migraines , nothing .
So , for argument 's sake , let 's just pretend like I 'm not crazy .
All right , walk with me .
There have been cases of transplant recipients
who have actually shown characteristics of their donor .
- Right , it 's called cellular memory . - Yeah .
There was a liver transplant patient in Kentucky last year ,
almost immediately felt the urge to pick up smoking , a health nut her entire life .
- The donor was a chain smoker ? - Down to the same brand .
And a few years ago , this little girl helped the police
solve the murder of the person she got her heart from .
She kept having visions of the crime .
There 's some kind of chemical , it 's ...
Peptides . That 's how the mind and body communicate .
So it 's not too big a leap to suggest
that memories can also be accessed from these organs , too .
No , because corneas aren 't a major organ . It 's like changing the windshield on a car .
But there 's still a chance , isn 't there ?
I ... I need that chance .
I need to find out who the donor was .
I see her in the mirror every day .
I have to find out who she was .
That is confidential information .
You can 't ask me to do that .
I could lose my licence .
Your licence ?
Well , by all means , hold on to that licence .
Sydney , come on .
Thank you .
- What floor ? - 14 .
Excuse me .
Sorry .
Thank you .
He 's here , isn 't he ?
My Tomi .
What was that about ?
Who 's Tomi ?
Her son .
Where was he ?
He 's dead .
Who are you ?
What do you want ?
I wanna help you .
But how can I if you won 't even tell me ?
Sydney ?
Are you OK ?
Sydney , open up . Open up .
Sydney , open up !
What the hell is going on ?
- I need to find out who she is . - Who ?
My donor . Her eyes ... My eyes . I 'm seeing what she saw .
- I 'm seeing what killed her . - Sydney , please .
Helen , don 't . I love you , but there 's no way you can help me .
You 're not making sense .
It 's all happening to me .
Everything that happened to her is happening to me .
Until I find out who she is
and what she wants , it 's gonna keep happening .
County General , please .
Hey ! Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
The only cornea transplant that matches the day of your surgery
came from Clínica de Santa Javiera in Los Llanos .
Your donor was from Mexico .
- Do you get carsick ? - Why ?
It 's a 15-hour drive .
Thank you .
The file says your donor was Ana Christina Martínez .
One living relative , mother , worked in a ceramics factory .
Hopefully , we can track her down .
So what made you change your mind ?
About what ?
About coming down here with me .
Why don 't you just let me sabotage my career in peace ?
I was just wondering why you changed your mind , that 's all .
Is it because you believe me ?
Paul , stop the car .
What did you see ?
There was a fire here . I keep seeing fire .
Well , maybe they know something .
- Hola , chico . - Hola .
Sabes qué pasó aquí ?
Las puertas estaban cerradas . Y solo algunos ...
He says all the doors were locked . And nobody could get out .
Mi hermano se murió .
He ... he lost a brother .
How did it happen ?
Cómo empezó el fuego ?
Todo fue culpa de la bruja .
He says something about a witch .
Vámonos .
- La bruja de Abasolo . - Abasolo ?
Qué es Abasolo ?
Dígame .
See that , " bruja " ?
Yeah . I 've seen it before .
What 's it mean ?
It means witch .
I don 't think anyone 's here .
Anybody home ?
Hello ?
Hello . How can I help ?
Hola , señor Martínez ?
No , I work here .
Is someone from the Martínez family here that we can speak to ?
Well , señora Martínez is here , but she 's resting .
Erm , well , we can wait . It 's important .
Emilio .
Está bien . Come in .
- Come in . - Thank you .
Please don 't be long . She 's not well .
Mrs Martínez , my name is Sydney Wells , and this is my friend , Dr Paul Faulkner .
What do you want ?
Erm ...
We would like to talk to you about your daughter .
I was wondering about how she died .
- What business is this of yours ? - It 's hard to explain .
You see , I have a connection
with your daughter .
Dios mío .
You have her eyes ?
I 'm sorry for how I look . There was a fire in the factory where I worked .
- Did your daughter die in the fire ? - No .
But many others did .
If they had listened to Ana , they would have been saved .
- What do you mean by that ? - It doesn 't matter now .
Did Ana ever ...
see things she couldn 't explain ?
Do you see things ?
- Things that are not real ? - Yeah .
It 's a terrible thing to see the spiritual world , isn 't it ?
To see souls destined to repeat their death every day ,
- .. and unable to find peace . - Yeah .
Ana was always alone .
People around here , they were always afraid of her .
- They would blame her . - Why would they blame her ?
Sometimes , when she was a little girl ,
she would sit in front of some person 's house
and she would just cry .
And soon after , somebody in that house would die .
I knew that she wasn 't doing these things , she wasn 't bringing death to anyone .
- But she just could ... - .. see death .
This is a small town , many superstitions .
Bruja . The graffiti outside ?
Guess no one has anything better to do all day than to cover your house in this ...
- Call an ambulance . - What ?
Call an ambulance !
Paul !
Every night ... Every night she does it again and again .
Please save her . Save her .
- S.. Save her . Save her . - What happened ?
She 's having a heart attack , we better get her to a hospital .
Would you help me put her in the car ?
- Ready ? Together . - Yeah .
- Where 's your keys ? - They 're in my right-hand pocket .
OK , open the door ! Right , bring her around . Put her head in first .
Sit her ... sit her inside , go round the other side . Pull her in , head first .
- Can you hold her legs for me ? - I got it .
- Please . Please save her . - All right , all right , close your door .
Close your door . Emilio , take the keys . You drive , you know the way .
Hurry up .
Vamos ! Come on !
- I need to stay here . - What ?
I 'm ... I 'm fine , just go .
All right , we 'll be quick . Don 't go anywhere !
All right , Ana , I 'm here .
What do you want me to see ?
- Where 's mom ? - Shut up , witch .
- Where 's my mom ? - Shut up .
- Listen , you have to ... - Get out of here !
- Please , where 's my mom ? - Get out !
Mom ! No ! I 'm not leaving . Mom !
Mom !
- Mom ! She needs to get out . Mom ! Mom ! - Hey ! Hey !
- What 's going on ? - Nothing . Get back to work .
- Who was here ? - No one ! Get back to work !
All of you ! What are you doing ? Get back to work ! Get back to work !
Oh , my God !
Mom ! Mom !
Mom !
Open the door !
Witch ! Witch !
- The witch ! - It 's the witch !
Paul ?
Paul , is that you ?
I need to be there with you .
Ana ?
I need to be here .
Ana .
Forgive me .
No ! No ! No ! Stop it !
Will you please stop ?
No !
No ! No ! No ! No !
No ! I can help you ! Ana !
Come on . Come on .
Come on . Come on . Come on .
What am I supposed to do ? Please tell me .
Your mother asked me to save you but I don 't know how .
What am I supposed to do ? I don 't know what to do here .
Please .
What ?
What do you want from me ?
Tell me .
Ana , please .
I tried to save them .
I believe you .
I see what you saw , I know what you went through .
I bel ... I believe you .
I tried to warn them .
It was never your fault .
How 's Mrs Martínez ?
She didn 't make it .
Thank you .
Hey , buddy , what 's going on ?
Er , some high-speed chase down the American side
has the whole border shut down for nearly an hour now .
You might as well make yourself comfortable .
Great , thanks .
How long was I out ?
Not very long .
It 's freezing .
What 's going on ?
I don 't know , there 's some kind of chase on the other side of the border .
- We 're gonna be here all night . - Oh , really ?
You wanna play a game ?
Mommy .
Come on , let 's get back in the car .
- You 're scaring the little girl , let 's go . - Wait .
Look at her , you 're scaring the hell out of her . Let 's get back in the car !
What ?
Oh , God .
Sydney !
Sorry about that , you all right ? Sorry .
I see the shadows , they 're everywhere .
Excuse me . Excuse me , please , open up !
- Open up , please ! - Let 's go .
Listen , there 's gonna be an accident , we don 't have a lot of time .
Please , just let me talk to the driver , OK ? Please !
- Miss , what are you ... - Let me handle this .
Oh , my God .
Don 't you understand ? This is what she wanted me to see .
Everything I dreamed wasn 't from Ana Christina 's life .
It was ... it was from this , right now .
She let me see that this was going to happen so I wouldn 't end up like her .
She wants me to save these people .
That 's what she wants me to do .
- Sydney ... - You have to believe me .
You have to believe me .
You need to get off this bus .
Everyone needs to get off this bus .
All of you , you can 't stay here .
Everyone , listen to me , you 've got to get off this bus .
- Come on , lady . - You need to get off this bus right now .
- Is it like a terrorist thing ? - Yes .
- Get up . Everybody get up . - That 's exactly what it is .
There 's a bomb on the bus . There 's a bomb on the bus !
There 's a bomb ! Run ! There 's a bomb , move it !
Everybody get out ! Get out !
Come on ! Come on ! Come on , get out of the car ! There 's a bomb on the bus !
Run , everyone , now ! Listen to me ! Run !
Get out of the car .
- Get out of your car now ! - 30 en camino .
- There 's a bomb on the bus ! - Come on ! Get out now !
- Come on ! - Go ! Go ! Go ! Go !
There 's a bomb ! Run ! Run !
Out of your cars !
- Wait here , sweetie . - What 's going on ?
Out of your cars ! Now !
- Everyone ! - Come on !
- Mom ! - Run !
- There 's a bomb , run ! Out of your car ! - Come on ! Run !
Come on ! Get those people out of there right now .
Out of your car ! Out of your car ! Get out of your car !
Come on .
Mom !
Hey , hey , you all right ?
- Get my daughter , she 's inside . - Is she in there ?
- Open the door ! - Help ! Please !
Please , someone help me !
Help ! Mom !
Stand back , I 'm gonna break your window .
Close your eyes . Stand back !
- Hurry ! - Stand back !
Come here , honey .
- Mom ! - Paul , let 's go !
- Hurry up ! - Mom !
- Come on , come on , come on . - Come on !
You saved them , Sydney .
You saved them .
Some say seeing is believing .
Now I know what they mean .
Ana Christina tried to prevent death .
But she was ultimately powerless to stop it .
Ana and I share both a blessing and a curse .
I know now , I don 't need eyes to see what truly matters .
The gift of Ana 's sight made me see what I was afraid to .
To use that vision , to not only save myself and others ,
but to give Ana the peace she never found in life .
( ¶ The Frequency : Stars )
¶ Look at the stars
¶ No matter where you are